/*--- Step 1 - Defining global variables ---*/

var questionsArray = [
    //Question 1
    {
        questionText: 'What is a quality of pre-competitive affect?',
        questionChoices: ['Low tension', 'Low depression', 'both'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 2,
        correctDetails: 'both low tension, and low depression are qualities of pre-competitive affect. '
    },

    //Question 2
    {
        questionText: 'What is a quality of emotional control?',
        questionChoices: ['preforming under pressure', 'getting fustrated with results', 'blaming others'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 0,
        correctDetails: 'performing under pressure is a staple to emotional control.'
    },

    //Question 3
    {
        questionText: 'what is a quality of emotional control?',
        questionChoices: ['having a wide array of emotions to both negetive and positive events', 'Responding to success and failure rationally', 'getting very excited with success'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 1,
        correctDetails: 'After a favorable big play reasonably celebrate with teammates After a negative play, listen and learn from mistakes.'
    },

    //Question 4
    {
        questionText: 'How fast is the fastest land speed record for cars?',
        questionChoices: ['593 mph', '843 mph', '763 mph'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 2,
        correctDetails: 'The official land-speed record (measured over one mile) is 1,227.985 km/h (763.035 mi/h) by Thrust SSC.'
    },

    //Question 5
    {
        questionText: 'How many car companies are there in the world?',
        questionChoices: ['Around 1500', 'Around 2500', 'Around 3500'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 2,
        correctDetails: 'There are more than 3500 Car Manufacturers worldwide.'
    },

    //Question 6
    {
        questionText: 'How much does an average person drive in a year?',
        questionChoices: ['About 13000 miles', 'About 15000 miles', 'About 20000 miles'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 0,
        correctDetails: 'About 13000 miles.'
    },

    //Question 7
    {
        questionText: 'How much does the average person in USA spend on gas each year?',
        questionChoices: ['$3400', '$1000', '$1300'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 2,
        correctDetails: 'About $1300.'
    },

    //Question 8
    {
        questionText: 'What is the best selling car in the world?',
        questionChoices: ['Volkswagen Beetle', 'Toyota Corolla', 'Ford Model T'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 1,
        correctDetails: 'Toyota Corolla sold 40000 cars worldwide.'
    },

    //Question 9
    {
        questionText: 'How long is the longest car in the world?',
        questionChoices: ['10feet', '65feet', '100 feet'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 2,
        correctDetails: 'A 30.5 m (100 ft) long 26-wheeled limousine was designed by Jay Ohrberg of Burbank, California, USA.'
    },

    //Question 10
    {
        questionText: 'What is price of the cheapest car in the world?',
        questionChoices: ['$1000', '$3000', '$2000'],
        questionCorrectChoice: 2,
        correctDetails: 'The Tata Nano is a city car manufactured in India with a price of US$2000 new.'
    }
];
/*--- Step 2 - Defining functions ---*/
/*--- Step 3 - Using functions ---*/
